Guide to the Cornell Migrant Program records, [ca. 1953-2005]
Cornell Migrant Program records, [ca. 1953-2005]
- Series XXVIII. Agricultural Work Force PWT and Immigrants in Rural Communities
  - Rural Opportunities Inc. involvement in immigration research project, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Worker survey and resident survey (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Progress reports, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Immigrants in the Community - Spanish and English Powerpoint (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - FRA planning meeting, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Sodus community discussions, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Sodus planning community meetings, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Drivers licenses meeting, 2004-06-02 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Sodus final public meeting, 2004-11 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Farm bureau and immigration project, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Cornell Migrant Program shut down and this project, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Limits of Social Capitol for Immigration Interrogation - Pfeffer and Parra, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - FRA - CD topics (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Strong Tires, Weak Ties - Pfeffer and Parra, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - Immigrants and the Community - Pfeffer and Parra, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - Ed Kissam Calif. FRA project (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - Banking and immigrants, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - Program work team - Agricultural Work Force, Family and Community (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - Program work team - Agricultural Work Force - Minutes and correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - Program work team - Opportunity for farmworkers within agricultural seminar, 2002-12 (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - Program work team - Vocational Education Seminar and McMahon Farm tour, 2003-05 (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - Program work team - Children's families' needs, 2003-08 (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - Program work team - Agriculture immigration policy seminar, 2003-11 (Box 31, Folder 48)
  - Program work team - Health needs seminar, 2004-07 (Box 31, Folder 49)
  - Program work team - Vocational education survey, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 50)
  - Program work team - Vocational education proposal, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 51)
  - Program work team - Disbanding (Box 31, Folder 52)
- Series XXIX: Alton Office - Kay Embrey, 1990-2005
  - Embrey position classification (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Resume - Embrey (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Annual reports - Embrey, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Recognition letters - Embrey (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Rural and Migrant Ministry - Ida Wells Award - Embrey, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Rural Opportunities Inc. - Farmworker Hall of Fame Award - Embrey, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Rural Opportunities Inc. - Farmworker Hall of Fame Award - Embrey, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - CITA recognition - Embrey, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence In and Out - Embrey, 1983-1989 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Support letters - Embrey (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - Embrey (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Leadership Institute - Kay's application (not accepted), 1985 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Lenten breakfast - Embrey, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Embrey - papers (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Brockport MEOP summer school - Embrey, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Nazareth College lectures - Embrey, 2003-2004 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Farmworker course - Embrey lecture, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Migrant Program annual report, 1988-1989 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Migrant Program Faculty Committee minutes and correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Migrant Program Faculty Committee minutes and correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Cornell Mirant Progran Faculty Advisory Board meeting, 1989-1990 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Plans of work and future plans, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Change of offices in Alton, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Black Focus: N. Rose-Wolcott tutorials and literacy project, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Cornell Migrant Program mailing list, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Alton office budget, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Wayne County staff positions (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - A Cultural Perspective of MFS and Substance Abuse Conference, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Science Intern Program (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Cornell Migrant Program update - Report, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Hispanic studies class lecture - Embrey, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Access to labor camps, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Sodus School - School to Work, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Cornell Migrant Program report, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Wayne Cornell Cooperative Extension correspondence (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Guestworkers workshop, 1998-06 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Jaun Marinez visit, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Cornell Migrant Program strategic plan, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Pilar Parra's class visit, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Dairy workers proposal to Smith-Lever - Embrey, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Wells College panel, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - SED reports, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Mr. Moreno (Mexico Senate) visit, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - SED reports - Embrey, 2000-2004 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - Pilar Parra's class visit annually, 1999-2003 (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Agrilink - DeMarree info, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Maria Cook's class lecture, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - Sodus teacher insurance - Embrey, 2004-02 (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - Cornell Migrant Program report (Box 33, Folder 49)
  - Changes in labor force - Letter to tutorials, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 50)
  - Translation project - Betty (Box 33, Folder 51)
  - Diversity training proposal, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 52)
  - Betty Garcia-Mathewson (Box 33, Folder 53)
  - Eduardo Gonzalez paper (Box 33, Folder 54)
  - Faith Richardson (Box 33, Folder 55)
  - John Joyce (Box 33, Folder 56)
  - Planning for 25 year conference not held, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 57)
  - 30th anniversary conference save the date card, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 58)
  - Anniversary conference brochure, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 59)
  - Anniversary conference registration list, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 60)
  - Conference materials (Box 33, Folder 61)
  - Anniversary dinner, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 62)
  - 30th anniversary dinner slide show (Box 33, Folder 63)
  - Our Roots - Program history, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 64)
  - Display board (Box 33, Folder 65)
  - Conference presentations - English and Spanish, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 66)
  - Anniversary conference - Farmworker tour, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 67)
  - Conferences - SED and CASD meetings, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 68)
  - Conference planning, 2001-2002 (Box 33, Folder 69)
  - Speaker correspondence, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 70)
  - Conference and dinner photos (Box 33, Folder 71)
  - Migrant children stats - New York State (Box 33, Folder 72)
  - Enumerating migrant farmworkers in New York State, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 73)
  - Cliff Demay (Box 33, Folder 74)
  - Joyce Lehman (Box 33, Folder 75)
  - Stuart Mitchell (Box 33, Folder 76)
  - Maps (Box 33, Folder 77)
- Series XXX: Labor Management - California
  - Citrus-Avocado Supervisors Handbook - Smith, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Fringe Benefit - Califoria, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Management Aids - Calififornia EDD, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Agricultural Personnel Management Forum - California, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Agricultural Personnel Management Forum - California, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Agricultural Personnel Management Forum, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Agricultural personnel management forum, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Farm personnel management - Manner, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Howard Rosenberg papers, 1981-1989 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Trends in Humn Resources Management newsletters - Rosenberg, 1980-1984 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Personnel Management of Lettuce Harvest Crews - Rosenberg, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Getting Up and Keeping in Personnel Management - Rosenberg, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Short Course for California Agricultural Career System, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - California Hired Farm Labor and Law Booklets, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Publications on California rural communities, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - California Special News - Merced County, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Written company policies and praticies - Johnson, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Labor stabilization proposal - Johnson, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Agricultural briefs - Bayer, California, 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Papers by Philip Martin, 1983-1996 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - California labor law postings and literature, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Limoneria Company, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - SAMCO - Ralph DeLeon, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Gary Johnson's materials, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Laws affecting farm employment in California, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Perspectives: Issues in Personnel Management - Fracisco, 1985-1989 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Billikopf quarterly reports, 1981-1984 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Individualized Instruction: Teaching Vocational Skills - Billikopf, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Agricultural personnel management newsletter - Sutter, California, 1991-1995 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Agriculture employment testing - Billikopf, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - People in Agriculture - Billikopf, 1982-1985 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - People in Agriculture - Billikopf, 1986-1988 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - People in Agriculture - Billikopf, 1989-1991 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - People in Agriculture - Billikopf, 1992-1996 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Labor management in agriculture instructor's manual - Billikopf, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Labor management in agriculture - Billikopf, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Rural California reports, 1989-2000 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Series XXXI. Farmworker Rights in New York and Other States
  - Press, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Press, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Press, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Press, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Press, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Olga Mendez (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Farmworkders union - Hudson Valley (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Separate and unequal - Senate Hispanic task force, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - CITA (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Rural and Migrant Ministry western - Press (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Rural and Migrant Ministry project grants (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Rural and Migrant Ministry epistle Sundays (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Rural and Migrant Ministry literature (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Rural and Migrant Ministry coins of change (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Rural and Migrant Ministry newsletters (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Rural and Migrant Ministry covenanting (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Rural and Migrant Ministry 20th anniversary (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - FAST - Rural and Migrant Ministry materials, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Rural and Migrant Ministry and CITA - Marching Forward reception photos - Rochester, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Rural and Migrant Ministry - Sewing Seeds dinner, New York City photos, 2003-2004 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Harvesting justice conference - Rochester, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Labor relatioins fast, 1996-1997 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Labor religous fast for farmworkers and photos, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Buffalo Community of Churches (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - New York State Community of Churches (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Labor - religious fast, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Labor - religious fast, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Labor - religious fast, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Labor - religious fast, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Freedom Ride, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Labor - religious fast, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Labor - religious fast, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - New York State labor - Religion coalition (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Syracuse Labor Council, 2000-09 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Testimonies - Joint T.F. hearing, Albany, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Labor Day Parade Rochester, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - AFL-CIO and farmworkers (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - AFL-CIO town meeting in Chester, 1999-10 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - CSEA region VI annual meeting, 2000-02 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - New York State senate hearing in Albany, 2000-02 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Nwe York State senate hearing in Warwick, 2000-03 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - New York State senate hearing in Albion, 2000-05 (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - Linda Lucas Browning (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - Cardinal O'Connor, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - Farmworker leaders recognition at Rural Opportunities Inc. annual meeting - Fall, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - Human Rights Day in Rochester, New York, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - B.E.O.C. (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - Farmworkers rights and Roman Catholics in New York (Box 32, Folder 48)
  - Sodus Episcopal Church presentation, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 49)
  - Unitarian - Canandaigua forum, 1998-2004 (Box 32, Folder 50)
  - First Unitarian - Rochester (Box 32, Folder 51)
  - Episcopal Church (Box 32, Folder 52)
  - Interfaith impact (Box 32, Folder 53)
  - National Farmworker Ministry (Box 32, Folder 54)
  - National Interfaith Committee for Farmworker Justice (Box 32, Folder 55)
  - National Interfaith Committee for Farmworker Justice - Rural Opportunities Inc. (Box 32, Folder 56)
  - Workplace project and Jennifer Gordon (Box 32, Folder 57)
  - Arturo Rodriguez, United Farmworkers and Wegmans, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 58)
  - Delores Huerta (Box 32, Folder 59)
  - UFW - California (Box 32, Folder 60)
  - UFW - Florida (Box 32, Folder 61)
  - National Farmworker Ministry (Box 32, Folder 62)
  - Teamsters - California (Box 32, Folder 63)
  - Lideres Campesinas - California (Box 32, Folder 64)
  - Teamsters - California (Box 32, Folder 65)
  - Voices of the Fields - California (Box 32, Folder 66)
  - Farm Labor Organizing Committee - Ohio (Box 32, Folder 67)
  - Farm Labor Organizing Committee - North Carolina (Box 32, Folder 68)
  - Coalition of Immokalee Workers - Florida (Box 32, Folder 69)
  - Coalition of Immokalee Workeres - Taco Bell Boycott (Box 32, Folder 70)
  - Pennsylvania mushroom workers (Box 32, Folder 71)
  - Farmworkers associate of Central Florida (Box 32, Folder 72)
  - Student Action with Farmworkers - North Carolina (Box 32, Folder 73)
  - Florida organizing (Box 32, Folder 74)
  - Florida newsletters (Box 32, Folder 75)
  - Oregon and P.C.U.N. (Box 32, Folder 76)
  - Washington State (Box 32, Folder 77)
  - Main advocate group, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 78)
  - Idaho student advocates (Box 32, Folder 79)
  - CATA - New Jersey (Box 32, Folder 80)
  - Texas (Box 32, Folder 81)
  - Farmworkers Union Network (Box 32, Folder 82)
  - Campaign for Labor Rights (Box 32, Folder 83)
  - Associate of Farmworker Opportunity Programs (AFOP) (Box 32, Folder 84)
  - Midwest Associaton of Farmworker Organization (MAFO) conferences (Box 32, Folder 85)
  - Mexican advocacy groups (Box 32, Folder 86)
  - Local campaign for sustainable farms (Box 32, Folder 87)
  - National campaign for sustainable agriculture (Box 32, Folder 88)
  - Northeast Organic Farming Association of New York (NOFA-NY) (Box 32, Folder 89)
  - Poultry industry (Box 32, Folder 90)
  - New York State attorney general's office (Box 32, Folder 91)
  - AFL-CIO of New York State (Box 32, Folder 92)
- Series XXXII. Agencies and Services in Wayne County and New York State
  - Wayne County farmworker population (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Wayne County - News stories - Workers (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Wayne County growers - News stories (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Kennedy in Wayne County (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Hope Village story, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Wayne outreach coordination, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Wayne County coalition of farmworker agencies, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Wayne County coalition of farmworker agencies, 1992-1994 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Wayne County coalition of farmworker agencies, 1995-1999 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Wayne County coalition of farmworker agencies, 2000-2004 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Finger Lakes consortium of farmworker agencies, 2004-2005 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Wayne County farmworker bus plan (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Wayne County services directory - English and Spanish, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Wayne County services directory, 2002-2004 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Seneca food closing - Wayne County, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Monroe/Orleans Genesee coalition (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Finger Lakes camp photo directory, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Finger Lakes camp photo and list, 2002-2003 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Camp permits - Department of Labor - Wayne County, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Orleans, Monroe camp list (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Oswego agency coalition (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Oswego services directory, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Service directory - Monroe area, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - State farmworker agency directions, 1990-2000 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Labor housing - Wayne County, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Wayne housing consortium (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Mexican Migrant Farmworkers Perception of Services, Wayne County - Zelaya, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Survey of migrant farmworkers in Wayne County, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - East Bloomfield MEOP (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Child care and ABCD (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Farmworker law project (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - FLSNY (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - FLNSY - Domestic violence project (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Inadequate defense services for farmworkers in New York, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Farmworkers meeting w/Govea - Thorbourne FE., 2001 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - FLSNY - FWI initial meeting, 2000-10 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - FWI board Of directors (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - FWI newsletter (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - FLSNY - Farmworker women's institute - Geneva group (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - FWI Sodus group (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - FWI - Women farmworker rights booklets (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Domestic violence - Wayne County project (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Women's rights - Rural Opportunities Inc. workshop, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - FWI - Immigrant women policy roundtable, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - FWI - Center for Women in Government roundtable, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - FWI and meeting with state comptroller, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - Immigrant Women and Violence Conference in New York City, 2002-09 (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - FWI information for commissioner of health, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - FWI - Center for women in government newsletter, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - Immigrant women access to reproductive health, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - Rural Opportunities Inc. Wayne County (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - Rural Opportunities Inc. correspondence (Box 35, Folder 52)
  - Rural Opportunities Inc. Wayne County housing (Box 35, Folder 53)
  - Food distribution, Rural Opportunities Inc. and Sarah Pines, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 54)
  - Western New York guide to services - Rural Opportunities Inc., 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 55)
  - Catholic Charities of Florida (Box 35, Folder 56)
  - Farmworker conference - Catholic diocese, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 57)
  - Hispanic ministry - Catholic (Box 35, Folder 58)
  - Wayne County public health - MSFW program, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 59)
  - Finger Lakes migrant health care project (Box 35, Folder 60)
  - Hudson Valley health (Box 35, Folder 61)
  - Oak Orchard Health Center and immunization project, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 62)
  - Wayne Finger Lakes tutorial (Box 35, Folder 63)
  - Wayne Finger Lakes tutorial - Planned activities, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 64)
  - Multicultural library - Wayne Finger Lakes tutorial, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 65)
  - Eastern farmworkers, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 66)
  - Wayne County apprentice farmer program, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 67)
  - H2A in New York (Box 35, Folder 68)
  - Housing/Camps - New York (Box 35, Folder 69)
  - Housing/Camps - New York State funding (Box 35, Folder 70)
  - Housing conference and follow up - Rural Opportunities Inc. (Box 35, Folder 71)
  - Farmworker housing in New York State - Rural Opportunities Inc. Report, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 72)
  - Housing - New York sanitary code and changes, 1996-1997 (Box 35, Folder 73)
  - Camps - Telephones (Box 35, Folder 74)
  - Genesee County (Box 35, Folder 75)
  - King Ferry camps (Box 35, Folder 76)
  - Monroe County, Brockport (Box 35, Folder 77)
  - Brockport - Day of the Dead celebrations (Box 35, Folder 78)
  - Niagara County and workers (Box 35, Folder 79)
  - Onondaga County services list, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 80)
  - Ontario County (Box 35, Folder 81)
  - Orange County and workshop (Box 35, Folder 82)
  - Orleans County workers (Box 35, Folder 83)
  - Slavery case - Garcia, Orleans County (Box 35, Folder 84)
  - Oswego County (Box 35, Folder 85)
  - Putman County (Box 35, Folder 86)
  - Tompkins/Cortland counties (Box 35, Folder 87)
  - Suffolk County and Farmville Day Haul (Box 35, Folder 88)
  - Ulster County (Box 35, Folder 89)
  - Yates County (Box 35, Folder 90)
  - Labor - Religion fast in Wayne County, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 91)
  - Juan Cavasos - artist (Box 35, Folder 92)
  - MiRanchito rodeos (Box 35, Folder 93)
  - State tour by Cornell Migrant Program staff, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 94)
- Series XXXIII. Communications
  - Consortium call, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Migrant messages, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - NASDME news, 1996-1997 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Memo, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Memo, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Memo, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Memo, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Memo, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Memo, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Memo, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Memo, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - News and Views, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - News and Views, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - News and Views, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - News and Views, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - News and Views, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - News and Views, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Kay's clips - Naming and feedback, 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Survey for Kay's clips, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Kay's clips, 2000-01-2000-03 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Kay's clips - National, 2000-07-2000-11 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Kay's clips - New York, 2000-07-2000-11 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Kay's clips, 2000-05-2000-06 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Kay's clips - New York, 2000-09-2000-11 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Kay's clips, 2000-09-2000-11 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Kay's Clips - national, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Kay's clips - New York, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Kay's clips - National, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Kay's clips - New York, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Kay's clips - New York, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Kay's clips - national, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Kay's Clips - last transmission, 2005-01 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous, 1961-1990 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1990-2006 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Chris Pawelski miscellaneous, 2001-2003 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Series XXXIV. Photographs and Slides
  - Cornell Migrant Program office - New office, 1975-1989 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Lula Sneed - Sewing instructor (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Sewing and fashion show, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Sewing and fashion show, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Fashion show, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Sewing and fashion show, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Fashion show, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Fashion show, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Sewing and fashion show, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Sewing and fashion show, 1980-1989 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Summer picnics (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Summer picnic, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Summer picnic, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Nutrition classes, 1980-1989 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Women in agriculture, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Tractor courses (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Harvest series computer class, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Harvest series fishing class (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - First aid classes, 1982-1984 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Harvest series, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Harvest series - Government class (Box 37, Folder 21)